{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340658180","data":{"timestamp":" 947340658180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k_pya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340664581","data":{"timestamp":" 947340664581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k_pya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340673777","data":{"timestamp":" 947340673777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340682905","data":{"timestamp":" 947340682905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340691306","data":{"timestamp":" 947340691306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340702812","data":{"timestamp":" 947340702812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_yo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340720581","data":{"timestamp":" 947340720581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_ji"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340733470","data":{"timestamp":" 947340733470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_ji"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340755254","data":{"timestamp":" 947340755254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_i"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340779417","data":{"timestamp":" 947340779416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340785946","data":{"timestamp":" 947340785946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340805586","data":{"timestamp":" 947340805586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t_pe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340845529","data":{"timestamp":" 947340845529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ake"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340859863","data":{"timestamp":" 947340859863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340882100","data":{"timestamp":" 947340882100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u_epo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340889591","data":{"timestamp":" 947340889591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u_epo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340905914","data":{"timestamp":" 947340905914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340919317","data":{"timestamp":" 947340919317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" c399cf3e-84a9-429b-886d-5ed19531ed25"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_c_ako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340962249","data":{"timestamp":" 947340962249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bili"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340969877","data":{"timestamp":" 947340969877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bili"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340979031","data":{"timestamp":" 947340979031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bili"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340990730","data":{"timestamp":" 947340990730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eusi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341026760","data":{"timestamp":" 947341026760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eusi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341035970","data":{"timestamp":" 947341035970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eusi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341050200","data":{"timestamp":" 947341050200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__bele"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341075467","data":{"timestamp":" 947341075467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ete"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341119678","data":{"timestamp":" 947341119678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ete"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341128854","data":{"timestamp":" 947341128854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ete"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341149092","data":{"timestamp":" 947341149091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ebu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341171099","data":{"timestamp":" 947341171099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__lila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341179287","data":{"timestamp":" 947341179287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__lila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341188503","data":{"timestamp":" 947341188502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__lila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341265712","data":{"timestamp":" 947341265711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__embe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341275096","data":{"timestamp":" 947341275096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__embe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341283557","data":{"timestamp":" 947341283556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__embe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341310484","data":{"timestamp":" 947341310484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ote"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341326968","data":{"timestamp":" 947341326968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__hule"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341333011","data":{"timestamp":" 947341333011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__hule"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341342730","data":{"timestamp":" 947341342730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__hule"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341355956","data":{"timestamp":" 947341355955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341365902","data":{"timestamp":" 947341365902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341374635","data":{"timestamp":" 947341374635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947341375720","data":{"timestamp":" 947341375720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_171022"," gameId":" 71f21d77-f40c-4a41-a90b-0de0260a416d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}